YASSINE

GAFSI

Tunis-Tunisia ,208034290 ↑ +90 534 786 6912 **** yassine.gaf@gmail.com **** Yassine Gafsi **i**



OBJECTIVE

A job with a well-respected firm, which utilizes my knowledge and the discipline and focus that I bring to my work. I am committed to developing my career path and to expand on the work experience I gained.

Results-focused Marketing inside Sales Representative, successful in revenue generation and member action, including sales and lead generation. Self-motivated with excellent verbal and written communication skills, as well as strong computer and customer relationship management (CRM) experience.



EDUCATION

IT Engineering Student (Online) | Polytechnique Internationale -Tunis-Tunisia- 2017-2018

Bachelor of Science: License IT Embedded system | Ecole Polytechnique Méditerranéenne – Tunis, Tunisia -2016-2017

Bachelor of Science: License IT embedded system | Institut Supérieur de l'informatique -Tunis, Tunisia – 2012-2015

Baccalaureate informatics | Lycée Attarine - Ariana-Tunisia -2011



WORK HISTORY

Project Manager | Elite-Tunis, Tunisia 07/2017 - 05/2018

- -New business development
- -Foreign Client/Partnership Sourcing
- -Client Relationship Management
- -Networking
- -New service Implementation
- -Training Development & Implementation
- -Video Design
- -Social Media Management
- -Community Liaison Management
- -General business solutions resulting in increased company exposure, Customer Traffic, and sales.

End-of-studies Internship | Tunisie Telecom – Tunis, Tunisia 01/2017 – 06/2017

-Developed end-user technical support application for IPMSAN system.

Inside Sales Representatives – MENA Region | Insider-Istanbul, Turkey 09/2016 – 12/2016

- -Warm Lead Generation
- -Outbound Lead Generation
- -Sales prospecting
- -Networking
- -Referral generation
- -Cold Calling
- -Client Relationship Management

Sales Representatives Specialist – MENA Region | Atex Automotive-Istanbul, Turkey 05/2016 – 09/2016

- -Developing sales performance
- -Building relationship with new & existing customers
- -New business development
- -Client relationship management
- -New partnership cultivation
- -Problem solving
- -Outbound calling
- -Cold emailing



SKILLS

- Programming Languages: C, C++, PHP5, SQL, PL/SQL.
- Data Base Management Systems: MYSQL, Oracle 10g.
- Web: HTML, JavaScript, CSS.
- Operating System: Windows, Linux.
- Tools & IDE: Eclipse, Visual Studio, NetBeans, Microsoft Office.



LANGUGES & CERRTIFICATIONS

- Bilingual Arabic /French
- Fluent English (certified)
- Microsoft Office Specialist Office Word® 2013.
- Microsoft Office Specialist Office Excel® 2013.
- Microsoft Office Specialist Office PowerPoint[®] 2013.



PROFESSIONAL REFRENCES

-Ridha CHAARA

CEO

ELITE

+216 98348458

ridha.chaara@gnet.tn

-Nizar Haj Ferjani

IT SUPERVISORY CHIEF

Tunisie Telecom

+216 682933

hnizar14@gmail.com

-Muhammed Yildirim

Country Manager

Insider

+97 1555194235

My@muhammedyildirim.com

-Atilla Cirtlik

Regional Head of sales

Atex

+90 5071703386

Atilla.cirtlik@gmail.com